We must inspire the people of Saga to rise up and resist as one!
We can rid this country of the crooks who have taken over everything!
This time, the samurai of Saga will prevail!
Yugiri!
Thanks for the medicine. I'm sorry to trouble you for it.
Has your grandfather's condition improved recently?
There hasn't been much change. He mostly stays in his bed.
Even though I've finally figured out a way for us to reclaim Saga.
You seem to have plenty of comrades on your side now.
Yes, I do. And as a matter of fact, we've all been putting together a petition.
See? Look at it. We're taking this straight to the prefectural magistrate.
We're also going to talk to as many of the elders around here as possible.
I'm sure that'll make a sizable difference.
Right?
How can we accomplish anything with you acting like such a coward?
You're no samurai! Step outside!
It's time someone beat some sense into you!
It sounds like they're getting kind of worked up.
I should go in and intervene.
Excuse me?
How dare you!
I don't care if it's disrespectful. I'm telling you the truth!
I do it. And I'm not even iveling. I love you!
It's all in fun!
He offered to take a photograph of us at no cost!
Right.
If this sample picture is enough to attract more customers,
then that's one step on the journey to revitalizing Saga.
Lord Ito,
is there a reason that you don't want your photograph taken?
Wait a minute.
I think I know what's happening.
I know what's happening.
Wait a minute. I think I know what's happening.
Are you afraid it's going to steal your soul?
Of course not!
You don't need to be scared. That's only a superstition.
I told you, that's not it.
I'm about to take the picture now.
You need to hold still, please.
Get ready.
Either way, it'll be nice to have.
Sure will.
I know it's a bit early, but let's go get a drink, shall we?
Actually, there's something else I need to take care of.
So Momozaki.
But there's always next time. Bye, you giddy.
Saga's old ruling class.
I'm assuming those men must be survivors of the war.
You should be careful.
What makes you say that, my lord?
I am sorry.
I was afraid to go on.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Those damn merchants finally came around.
This should keep us afloat for a while.
And Sir Momozaki.
Should we let him in on this, too?
Don't bother with that.
Let's concentrate on the weapons.
Those cannons Naveshima's bringing from Tsukiji will be in place to target the main road to Nagasaki, right?
on the weapons. Those cannons Naveshima is bringing from Tsukiji will be in place to
target the main road to Nagasaki, right? Yes, one of the merchants gave me his word.
For better or for worse, Kiiichi is the one who accepted them as comrades in his efforts to
save Saga. I suppose what will be will be. This world will always be shaped by the actions of men.
That's karma for you.
Lord Kiiichi says you haven't been taking the medicine I sent you. Can you explain to me why
that is? It's pointless. I am Saga. No, Saga is me. If this land is to fade from existence,
then there'll be nothing left of me either. So despite Lord Kiiichi's efforts to bring change,
you believe that Saga's fate is set in stone? Kiiichi is special. Even in these dark times,
I can see that the star of Saga's salvation shines over him. But this is life and death
now, and only the hands of men control such things. With the state I'm in, I don't have
enough strength to offer him any real help. Here, drink this, sir. That terrible medicine
that I just told you.
It may be unpleasant, but take it every day until the box is empty.
Wait, just hang on a second.
All this anger we're feeling, and you think a measly petition will solve everything?
But you don't understand. Please hear me out. It's not like we're trying to start a war here.
Forget about that. What we need now more than anything else is action.
If everyone could give me a little more time to work, then I swear we'll be able to get our Saga back.
What does a child like you know? Nothing. You could never understand how it felt for us to watch Saga die eight years ago.
Had enough yet?
You did everything that you could do, but the only path ahead of you now is destruction.
The Saga war survivors are arming themselves. The army won't ignore that.
What happened eight years ago is about to be repeated.
It takes more than ideals to change the world.
I can't believe you still haven't wrapped your head around that fact.
But what's going to happen to the place we love if I just give up now?
If I lose hope, then so will everybody else.
They'll think Saga's a lost cause, and they'll stop trying forever.
It can't end that way.
This should be a place where you can live the life that you've always dreamed of,
regardless of where you were born or what kind of background you have.
Where you can reach for the future and help your friends do the same.
It'll be just like the Saga we had before, but better.
Wake up, would you?
You sound like a stupid little kid.
This country is still immature.
It's twisted and barbaric.
It'll crush you underfoot like you're a weak piece of dirt.
Stop talking like it's over!
All of this is only the beginning for Saga!
You?
Oh?
If this keeps up,
Kichi will be a fugitive.
He might not have meant to,
but his actions sparked a rebellion.
You should get out of Saga for a while.
I wasn't joking about what I said.
I think the two of you could really try-
Lord Ito,
you may act as though you see Lord Kichi's ambitions
as frivolous and shallow,
but is that true?
Look, Kichi's a real idiot.
Helpless and painfully shy.
But he's so damn determined.
That's why I have to.
Look after him for me.
Thank you very much, sir.
Thank you.
Forget about that.
What we need now more than anything else is action.
Who are you?
You're
This is exactly why I said to stop.
Ito, why would you? How could you do this? I don't understand.
Tell me, Keeji. Will you give up now? Does this change your mind?
My job is to keep an eye out for rebels lurking within Saga.
It would have been fine if you'd kept your childish campaign.
But now you've taken it a step too far.
Ito, no.
This is all that I have.
I told you this place is barbaric.
It's full of people who are like me.
The kind of people who don't know any other way to live.
We'll say something.
Ito, please stop.
Keeji, run!
They're not going to stop searching.
You must leave Saga, at least for now.
Why did this happen?
I never fully understood the situation.
But now, Ito and my comrades, it's my fault!
All mine!
I stirred this whole thing up and now everyone is dead!
I'm a fool!
I can't create a new Saga!
Please, just go.
You're only after me, and I don't care anymore.
You don't have to die.
I've heard enough whining, Lord Keeji.
While it may be true that this dream you've been chasing after is childish at best and impossible at worst,
that dream was the catalyst that finally began to bring actual change,
and now you have a responsibility to see it through to the end.
Many of the hearts you inspired are no longer beating,
so you must ensure that your dream comes true,
or their lives will have been lost for nothing!
You truly believe that a new Saga would bring back the way of life we long for, don't you?
Even when you were mocked for it, you had faith and pressed on.
If you turn your back on that, your efforts will be wasted.
Go through Mitsusei Pass, then take a boat from Hakata to Nagasaki.
After that, read the letter, and then you'll know what to do.
I've asked a few of my oldest friends to assist you.
Trust me, if you have their support, then no one will ever harm you.
Even the government can't touch you.
It's not much, but it's all that I can offer.
After you survive this, the next step will be up to you.
My Lord, I long to see the Saga that only you could create.
Make me proud.
I swear, on my very life, I'll establish a new Saga.
It'll be everything we dreamed of.
This is a surprise, even from the legendary courtesan.
Who was it that set you free, Yugiri?
There's something known as the sheathed Kichiemon.
Have you ever heard of it, my Lord?
The demon of Hibia.
I'd better take this seriously, then.
And then it's all the time to do something to do.
You
I'm sorry, I guess you're stuck with the short end of the stick, but why a
Place that people can be free to live out the lives that they desire
I
By the time this letter finds its way into your hands
It's more than probable I am no longer alive
A few of my old acquaintances have agreed to look after Lord Kiichi going forward
However, after the blood that's been spilled and with the increasing signs of rebellion in Saga
Someone must accept the responsibility and be punished
In the end, this entire incident, as well as my own involvement in it, will be treated as though it never happened
If Lord Kiichi inquires about me, please tell him that I was able to depart from Saga safely
As for you, if you truly are Saga itself, I trust that you will be a courageous guide for the new land that Lord Kiichi creates
Bring Saga into the future
This is goodbye
This, that is bye
This Jonginy is
ware
name
The End
Easy breezy zombies, no time to snooze, get moving already!
People's keisters are falling asleep out there!
Move! Let's go!
Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
Let's give them a good show, Yugi!
Right.
Sangha
Yeah
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! young
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
撮り直した真夜中 今夜は来る子ない川行いたく
何枚花びらちぎって リンドンリンドン
神話バラバラ鳴りそう 囚われの時計
ジキランジキランジキランジキラン
ジキランジキランジキランチキラン
星8号美人ブルー 集むにだってる噂
I told them that they accept it I will be
I will come
So let's live like a two,
Am I Firan?
I'm fundoing
how are you liking this era it's wonderful so far unsurprisingly entertaining such a large
audience is fun more so than i thought what are they called the saga et we call ourselves fran
shushu ah that was it that young man certainly created a fuss but it turns out it amounted to
something after all yes it did indeed who would have thought and i'm truly grateful
it's my turn to carry the torch now in present-day saga i plan to choose a path for myself
and walk bravely luckily i have comrades who share that goal
saki here if there's anyone i can't beat it's big sis but if our big comeback is at stake i won't lose to
anybody next time on zombieland saga revenge episode 10 the saga of how these zombies will get their
revenge watch it punks
you